Guide to the Stanford University, Department of History, Independent Study Program, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Department of History, Independent Study Program, records
1928-1945
SC0049
Stanford University. Department of History. Independent Study Program.
14 Linear feet
Student analyses of proposed independent studies program, minutes of the Committee on Independent Study Plan, and files regarding the organization and administration of the program.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
Administrative transfer, Dept. of Hisory, 1968.
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Description of the Collection
Student analyses of proposed independent studies program, minutes of the Committee on Independent Study Plan, and files regarding the organization and administration of the program.
Access Terms
Stanford University. Department of History. Committee on Independent Study Plan.; Stanford University. Department of History. Independent Study Program.; Minutes.
Collection Contents
- Records, 1928-1945
  - Independent Studies, 1932-1945
    Independent study analyses of and by the following students, arranged alphabetically.
    - Aaron-Abramson (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Ackerman-Adams (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Adams-Ahrens (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Ainsworth-Alexander (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Alexander-Allan (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Allen-Altman (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Alward-Anderson (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Anderson-Anderson (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Anderson-Arias (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Armstrong-Arnstein (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Arthur-Ayers (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Aynesworth-Baer (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Baer-Baker (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Baker-Barbash (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Barber-Barnett (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Barner-Bassett (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Bassi-Benèt (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Bennett-Bine (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Binney-Bold (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Bolton-Boyd (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Boyle-Browder (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Brown-Bryant (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Bryner-Burns (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Burris-Cannon (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Capers-Castle (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Caswell-Clarke (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Clayburgh-Collins (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Colombat-Cox (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Coyle-Crowe (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Crump-Davis (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Dawaff-Diamond (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Dibble-Drew (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Drewes-Dynes (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Eadie-Ellis (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Elzey-Fazen (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Fellows-Flavin (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Fleming-Frolik (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Frost-Gill (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Gillespie-Gould (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Goulter-Ground (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Grover-Hall (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Halla-Hanson (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Harcourt-Harvey (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Harwood-Henkel (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Henley-Hinsdale (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Hinton-Hooper (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Hoos-Hughes (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Hurlbert-Jackson (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Jacobs-Johnson (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Johnston-Kay (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Kayser-King (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Kingsburg-Kuzell (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Labbé-Leff (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Lehmann-Lewis (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Libbott-Livingston (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Lochrie-Lundell (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Lundin-McDaniel (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - McDearmon-McKinley (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - McLaren-Manning (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Mannon-Martineau (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Marvin-Mayock (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Means-Miller (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Millhauser-Montgomery (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Moore-Moulthrop (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Moulton-Myers (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Naftzger-Newman (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Newton-Nutting (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Oakford-Ownby (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Packard-Perham (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Perko-Poole (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Poore-Quinsey (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Rabjohn-Reel (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Regan-Rice (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Richardson-Robertson (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Robinson-Rubin (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Rude-Schaupp (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Scheeline-Schute (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Schutt-Sherriffs (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Shields-Slate (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Slatterly-Smith (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Snively-Stanwood (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Stapley-Stevens (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Stewart-Stotsky (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Stover-Swafford (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Swan-Taylor (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Telfeyan-Thornburg (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Thorne-Townsend (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Traylor-Tuttle (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Tweedy-Voss (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Wadsworth-Watson (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Wear-Wendt (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Werner-White (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Whitlock-Williams (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Williamson-Winter (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Wise-Wray (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Wright-Zucker (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Memoranda of Independent Study Program, 1928-1945; 1 box
    Memoranda folders include: Students enrolled in the program, circulars sent to students, reports to the General Educational Board on Independent Study, sample forms for student evaluation, and committee reports.
    - Memoranda of Independent Study Program, 1928-1929 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Memoranda of Independent Study Program, 1929-1930 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Memoranda of Independent Study Program, 1930-1931 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Memoranda of Independent Study Program, 1931-1932 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Memoranda of Independent Study Program, 1932-1933 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Memoranda of Independent Study Program, 1933-1934 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Memoranda of Independent Study Program, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Memoranda of Independent Study Program, 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Memoranda of Independent Study Program, 1936-1937 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Memoranda of Independent Study Program, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Memoranda of Independent Study Program, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Memoranda of Independent Study Program, 1938-1939 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Memoranda of Independent Study Program, 1939-1940 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Memoranda of Independent Study Program, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Memoranda of Independent Study Program, 1941-1942 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Memoranda of Independent Study Program, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Memoranda of Independent Study Program, 1942-1943 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Memoranda of Independent Study Program, 1943-1944 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Memoranda of Independent Study Program, 1944-1945 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Memoranda of Independent Study Program, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Departmental Orders, Requisitions, 1928-1945; 1 box
    - Financial, 1928-1933 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Financial, 1933-1934 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Financial, 1934-1935 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Financial, 1935-1936 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Financial, 1936-1937 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Financial, 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Financial, 1938-1939 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Financial, 1939-1940 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Financial, 1940-1941 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Financial, 1941-1942 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Financial, 1942-1943 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Financial, 1943-1944 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Financial, 1944-1945 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Minutes, Committee on Independent Study Plan, 1926-1931 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Minutes, Committee on Independent Study Plan, 1931-1934 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Minutes, Committee on Independent Study Plan, 1934-1935 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Minutes, Committee on Independent Study Plan, 1935-1938 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Minutes, Committee on Independent Study Plan, 1938-1944 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - 0 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Organization of Independent Study Program, 1925 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Organization, 1927 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Organization, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Organization, 1929 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Administration, 1930 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Administration, 1931 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Administration, 1932-1934 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Administration, 1935-1936 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Administration, 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Administration, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Administration, 1941-1942 (Box 8, Folder 30)